

Arman Ajabkhani

SENIOR JAVA DEVELOPER - BACK END

PROFILE

Gender: Male Nationality: Iranian Birth Date: 8/25/1983

I am a software engineer with more than 10 years'experience in software developing with Several roles including developer, designer, technical team lead in various projects.

Concentration, high interaction with teammates, responsibility and perseverance, key observations in operational environments and issue solving are my main characteristics.

Learning new concepts, distributed systems and Software Quality(functional and non-functional) are interesting and exciting for me.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science from Sheikh Bahaee Isfahan University in Software Engineering from September 2000 to September 2006.

LANGUAGES

English

Persian

CONTACT

Email: arm.khani@gmail.com

Mobile: +98 912 8589 456

LinkedIn: Arman Ajabkhani's profile

Address: No. 23, Parastoo2 Alley, Kaj St.,

Taherkhani St., Tehran, Iran

WORK EXPERIENCE

SNAPP(ride sharing service[www.snapp.ir])

Senior Java Developer

July 2019 - Present

My responsibility as a senior java developer in Fintech team.

- Designing and implementing new generation Financial management services for users and drivers.
- Providing services for more than 2 million users. Developing services with SpringBoot, Spring Cloud, MySql, OpenShift and Redis. Responsible for designing and development of Payment and Wallet Management Services.

Sava Arman Kish(Crypto-currencies Exchange start-up)

Senior Java Developer

Nov 2018 - Jul 2019

My responsibility as a senior java developer in the Exchange backend tean.

- Developing reactive java using RxJava and Vert.x and Swagger.
- Responsible for designing, development and maintaining user account and notification services.
- Designing and implementing features and fixing bug in several micro-services.

TOSAN(Payment and Banking solution provider)

Senior Java Developer /Team Lead

Nov 2011 -Nov 2018

My responsibility as a Team lead in Channel Manager Team : -

Mentoring, coaching, training and planning tasks for the team members.

- Analysis, Design, Development, Deployment and Maintenance several applications and micro-services.
- Designing and developing some complicated features in open banking API.

My responsibility as a senior java developer in Channel Manager Team:

- developing functionalities for tracking and authentication and authorization.
- developing and maintaining Exchange and Corporate Banking subsystems.
- providing serveral financial and payment services for front-end teams.
- developing and implementing RMI and Web Services (REST / SOAP JAX-WS).
- implementing many feature in Persistence layer using JPA/Hibernate

Elm o Sanat

Senior C#/ASP.NET Developer

Sep 2010 -Oct 2011

- implementing several new features in the School product.
- I used Entity Framework in school product and custom report generator.
- implementing virtual replication on SQL Server with use web service.

Netbina (Online Advertising)

Junior C#/ASP.NET Developer

Oct 2006 -Mar 2009

- implementing several functionalities for the advertising products.
- developing a several feature in Blog Service with C# and ASP.NET.



Arman Ajabkhani

SENIOR JAVA DEVELOPER - BACK END

PROGRAMMING SKILLS

Java / JVM	Spring
SOA/Micro-services	Spring Boot
Test Driven Development	Spring MVC
Event Driven Architecture	Spring Security
Software Architecture Patterns	Spring Cloud
Design Patterns	Spring Batch
Live Migration	Spring Data / JPA/ Hibernate
Concurrent Programming	Spring AOP / aspectj
Reactive Programming	Vert.x / RxJava
RESTful Web Services	Redis / Redisson
SOAP / JAX-WS /JAX-RS	Oracle
Docker	MySQL / SQL Server
OpenShift	Gradle / Maven
Jenkins/Gitlab CI/CD	Swagger UI/ Codegen
Financial / Banking / Payment Systems	Git / Subversion / TFS
Crypto Currency Exchanges	ActiveMQ/ Rabbit MQ
UML / Agile and RUP Methodologies	Apache Tomcat
Confluence / SharePoint / Documenting	OAuth / JWT
Jira / TFS / HP ALM	JUnit / TestNg / Mockito
Scrum	<u>C</u> #
Distributed Systems	LATEX